

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>http://localhost:4000/</id>
  <title>twseptian</title>
  <subtitle>A personal space where I share simple reflections, lessons, and small discoveries from my continuous journey in learning—whether in information security, penetration testing, CTF, or exploring data science and machine learning.</subtitle>
  <updated>2025-10-21T21:35:19+07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>twseptian</name>
    <uri>http://localhost:4000/</uri>
  </author>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml"/>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"
    href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator>
  <rights> © 2025 twseptian </rights>
  <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon>
  <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo>


  
  <entry>
    <title>From Burp to Claude: Quick MCP Integration Guide</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/from-burp-to-claude-quick-mcp-integration-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="From Burp to Claude: Quick MCP Integration Guide" />
    <published>2025-10-19T08:00:19+07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-10-19T08:00:19+07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/from-burp-to-claude-quick-mcp-integration-guide/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="http://localhost:4000/posts/from-burp-to-claude-quick-mcp-integration-guide/" />
    <author>
      <name>twseptian</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Technology" />
    
    <category term="AI" />
    
    <category term="Infosec" />
    
  

  <summary>Introduction Connecting Burp Suite to an AI model like Claude 1 2is straightforward using the Model Context Protocol (MCP). MCP acts as a bridge that lets AI tools consume real contextual data from your security tooling — not just plain text — enabling the model to leverage Burp’s intercepts, traces, and session context for more practical, context-aware analysis.  Installation  To get started, ...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Model Context Protocol (MCP): The Emerging Standard Connecting AI to the Real World</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/mcp-introduction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Model Context Protocol (MCP): The Emerging Standard Connecting AI to the Real World" />
    <published>2025-10-09T08:00:19+07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-10-09T08:00:19+07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/mcp-introduction/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="http://localhost:4000/posts/mcp-introduction/" />
    <author>
      <name>twseptian</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Technology" />
    
    <category term="AI" />
    
  

  <summary>Introduction As artificial intelligence continues to integrate into modern business operations, the need for a standardized way to connect AI models with real-world systems becomes more critical. The Model Context Protocol (MCP) addresses this challenge — an open standard that enables large language models (LLMs) and intelligent agents to interact securely with external tools, data sources, and...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>My Take on OSEP (PEN-300): Challenges, Lessons, and Real-World Relevance</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/osep-experience/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Take on OSEP (PEN-300): Challenges, Lessons, and Real-World Relevance" />
    <published>2024-12-12T20:00:19+07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2024-12-12T20:00:19+07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/osep-experience/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="http://localhost:4000/posts/osep-experience/" />
    <author>
      <name>twseptian</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Infosec" />
    
    <category term="Certification" />
    
  

  <summary>This is just a brief note from my own experience and from several other reviewers who have taken the OSEP   Reflecting on OSEP (PEN-300) — Worth Taking in 2024? Recently, I went through several reviews from OSEP / PEN-300 participants — along with reflecting on my own experience — and wanted to share a summary of the key takeaways, strengths, and lessons that might help others better understand...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>IoT Dataset Research: Curating Realistic Traffic for Security Analysis</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/iot-dataset-research/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IoT Dataset Research: Curating Realistic Traffic for Security Analysis" />
    <published>2023-12-12T20:00:19+07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-12-12T20:00:19+07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/iot-dataset-research/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="http://localhost:4000/posts/iot-dataset-research/" />
    <author>
      <name>twseptian</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Infosec" />
    
    <category term="IoT" />
    
    <category term="Research" />
    
  

  <summary>Introduction This article outlines my work in researching Internet of Things (IoT) security and producing curated datasets for intrusion detection, protocol analysis, and machine-learning experiments. The focus is on practical, reproducible methods for capturing and labeling traffic that reflects real deployment conditions. Links to the underlying records are provided for verification and reuse...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>My Journey in CVE Research: From Discovery to Disclosure</title>
    <link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/my-journey-in-cve-research-from-discovery-to-disclosure/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Journey in CVE Research: From Discovery to Disclosure" />
    <published>2023-12-01T20:00:19+07:00</published>
  
    <updated>2023-12-01T20:00:19+07:00</updated>
  
    <id>http://localhost:4000/posts/my-journey-in-cve-research-from-discovery-to-disclosure/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="http://localhost:4000/posts/my-journey-in-cve-research-from-discovery-to-disclosure/" />
    <author>
      <name>twseptian</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Infosec" />
    
    <category term="CVE" />
    
    <category term="Research" />
    
  

  <summary>Introduction Researching software vulnerabilities and contributing to the CVE ecosystem is both a technical challenge and a responsibility. This post highlights my personal experience in vulnerability research—how I discovered flaws, validated them safely, and worked through the disclosure process that eventually led to public CVE assignments.    Why I Pursue CVE Research My motivation stems fr...</summary>

  </entry>

</feed>


